Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy, Dean's Office; Records ua680
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Dean's Day Files, 1967-1982; 3; 0.33 cubic ft.
  This series also consists of Dean Tickner's day files of outgoing correspondence. These records include information relating to the Legislative Institute, the proposed planning program, Comparative Development Research Center (CDSC), research, faculty, Public Affairs Research Center (PARC), courses, Institute for Government Executives, Political Science Department, IPSA, Local Government Studies Center, recruitment, budgets, urban affairs program (1970), the organization of GSPA (1967) and includes organizational charts (1968-1969, 1970).
  - Tickner-Outgoing Correspondence, 1967 September 8-December 21 (Box 5 (3-Dean's Day Files), Folder 15)
  - Tickner-Outgoing Correspondence, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Dean's Day Files), Folder 16)
  - Tickner-Outgoing Correspondence, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Dean's Day Files), Folder 17)
  - Tickner-Outgoing Correspondence, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Dean's Day Files), Folder 18)
  - Tickner-Outgoing Correspondence, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Dean's Day Files), Folder 19)
  - Tickner-Outgoing Correspondence, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Dean's Day Files), Folder 20)
  - Tickner-Outgoing Correspondence, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Dean's Day Files), Folder 21)
  - Public Administration & Policy, 1977-1982 (Box 5 (3-Dean's Day Files), Folder 22)
- Academic Department and Program Files, 1968-1984; 4; 2.5 cubic ft.
  This series consists of the material related to Political Economy Program, 1972-1975; Political Science Department, 1971-1984; Public Administration Department, 1970-1984; and Public Affairs Program, 1972-1982
  - Political Economy Program, Meeting - On the Relationship Between Economics & Political Economy, October 2, 1972 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 1)
  - Political Economy Program, 1972 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 2)
  - Political Economy Program, 1972-1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 3)
  - Political Economy Program, Scheduling Request Sheet & Distribution of Course Forms (Political Economy), 1974 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 4)
  - Political Economy Program, Department of Economics & Political Economy - Setting Up Program Review, 1974 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 5)
  - Political Economy Program, Evaluation of Economics & Political Economy Programs - Domar, Nelson, Hansen, 1974 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 6)
  - Political Economy Program, Alternative Development Plan for Doctorate in Political Economy, 1975 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 7)
  - Political Economy Committee Meeting, 1975 February 24 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 8)
  - Political Economy Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 9)
  - Political Science Department, Promotions of Faculty, Political Science Department, 1971 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 10)
  - Political Science Department, Dean's Day File, 1971 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 11)
  - Political Science Department, Directory (SUNY), 1971-1972 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 12)
  - Political Science Department, Recruitment, 1972-1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 13)
  - Political Science Department, Report-Political Science Department (Diamant), 1972-1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 14)
  - Political Science Department, Minar's Report, 1972 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 15)
  - Political Science Department, Dean's Day File- Political Science Department, 1972 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 16)
  - Political Science Department, Directory - NYS Political Science Faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 17)
  - Political Science Department, Political Science Faculty Meeting, 1973 March 5 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 18)
  - Political Science Department, Political Science Faculty Meeting, 1973 March 8 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 19)
  - Political Science Department, Political Science Faculty Meeting, 1973 September 13 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 20)
  - Political Science Department, Political Science Faculty Meeting, 1973 September 20 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 21)
  - Political Science Department, Political Science Faculty Meeting, 1973 October 7 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 22)
  - Political Science Department, Political Science Faculty Meeting, 1973 October 11 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 23)
  - Political Science Department, Political Science Faculty Meeting, 1973 October 18 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 24)
  - Political Science Department, Political Science Faculty Meeting, 1973 November 7 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 25)
  - Political Science Department, Political Science Faculty Meeting, 1973 December 6 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 26)
  - Political Science Department, Dean's Day File - Political Science Department, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 27)
  - Political Science Department, 1974, Enrollments, Political Science Department, 1972-1974 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 28)
  - Political Science Department, 1974, Distribution of Courses Request Form, Political Science Department, 1972-1974 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 29)
  - Political Science Department, 1974, Dean's Day Files, Political Science Department, 1972-1974 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 30)
  - Political Science Department, 1973, Chairman, Political Science Department, 1972-1974 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 31)
  - Political Science Department, Course Descriptions, 1975-1976 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 32)
  - Political Science Department, Draft Report of the Assistant Professor's of the Political Science Dept - Status of Department & PhD Program, 1975-1976 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 33)
  - Political Science Department, Faculty Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 34)
  - Political Science Department, Publications Political Science Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 35)
  - Political Science Department, Origins & Descent of Various Lines, 1972; 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 36)
  - Political Science Department, Application & Enrollment Trends & Projections, Political Science, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 37)
  - Political Science Department, 1976-1977, POS650 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 38)
  - Political Science Department, Chairmanship (Political Science Department), 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 39)
  - Political Science Department,Political Science Dept. Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 40)
  - Political Science Department, Undergraduate Course Descriptions, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 41)
  - Political Science Department, Recruitment, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 42)
  - Political Science Department, Recruitment, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 43)
  - Political Science Department, Recruitment, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 44)
  - Political Science Department, Reviews of Political Science Faculty Appearing in Core Journals, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 45)
  - Political Science Department Reports, 1968-1984 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 46)
  - Public Administration Dept. - MPA Concentrations & DPA Residency Requirements, 1968 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 47)
  - Public Administration Department, Dean's Day File, Public Administration Department, 1970-1971 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 48)
  - Public Administration Department, Chairman Public Administration Dept., 1972 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 49)
  - Public Administration Department, Dean's Day File - Public Administration Department (2 folders), 1972 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 50)
  - Public Administration Department, Dean's Day File - Public Administration Department (2 folders), 1972 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 51)
  - Public Administration Department, President George Angell, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 52)
  - Public Administration Department, Public Administration Department Faculty Meeting, October 5, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 53)
  - Public Administration Department, Faculty Meeting, Public Administration Department, September 14, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 54)
  - Public Administration Department, Dean's Day File - Public Administration Department (3 Folders), 1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 55)
  - Public Administration Department, Dean's Day File - Public Administration Department (3 Folders), 1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 56)
  - Public Administration Department, Dean's Day File - Public Administration Department (3 Folders), 1973 (Box 6 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 57)
  - Public Administration Department, Spring 1975 Schedule (Public Administration Department), 1974 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 1)
  - Public Administration Department, Public Administration Department Meeting, November 15, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 2)
  - Public Administration Department, Distribution of Courses Form, Public Administration Department, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 3)
  - Public Administration Department, Public Administration Department Pamphlet - Rough Draft, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 4)
  - Public Administration Department, Dean's Day File - Public Administration Department, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 5)
  - Public Administration Department, Chairman Public Administration Department, 1974-1976 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 6)
  - Public Administration Department, Public Administration Department, Adjunct Professors, 1975-1976 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 7)
  - Public Administration Department, Enrollments, 1975-1976 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 8)
  - Public Administration Department, Public Administration Department Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 9)
  - Public Administration, Origins & Descent of Various Lines, Public Administration Department, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 10)
  - Public Administration, Evaluation of MPA & DPA Programs, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 11)
  - Public Administration, Course Descriptions, Public Administration Department, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 12)
  - Public Administration, Application & Enrollment Trends & Projections, Public Administration Department, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 13)
  - Public Administration, Review MPA & DPA, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 14)
  - Public Administration, Review MPA & DPA, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 15)
  - Public Administration, Public Administration Department Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 16)
  - Public Administration, Recruitment & Request to Fill a Vacancy, Public Administration Department, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 17)
  - Public Administration, Self-Study & Evaluation, Public Administration Department, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 18)
  - Public Administration, MPA Policy Analysis Concentration, 1978 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 19)
  - Public Administration, Department of Public Administration, 1977-1981 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 20)
  - Public Administration, Department of Public Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 21)
  - Public Administration, NASPAA Self Study Report - Master of Public Administration Program, Vol. I., 1980 July (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 22)
  - Public Administration, NASPAA Self Study Report - Master of Public Administration Program, Vol. II., 1980 July (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 23)
  - Public Administration, DPA Exams, 1980 Summer (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 24)
  - Public Administration, DPA Exams, 1981 January (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 25)
  - Public Administration, DPA Exams, 1982 Summer (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 26)
  - Public Administration, DPA Exams, 1983 Fall (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 27)
  - Public Administration, DPA Exams, 1984 Spring (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 28)
  - Public Affairs (Doctor of Arts in Public Affairs, ca. 1971 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 29)
  - Doctorate of Arts Degree in Public Affairs (Advisory Committee Doctor of Arts Degree in Public Affairs, 1972 December 18 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 30)
  - Doctorate of Arts Degree in Public Affairs (Advisory Committee Doctor of Arts Degree in Public Affairs, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 31)
  - Doctorate of Arts Degree in Public Affairs (Proposal for a Doctorate of Arts in Public Affairs, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 32)
  - Doctorate in Public Affairs (Doctorate in Public Affairs - Internal Evaluation Report, ca. 1973 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 33)
  - Doctorate in Public Affairs (NYC Faculty Council of Community College (DPA Proposal), October 4, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 34)
  - Doctorate in Public Affairs (Budget & Doctor of Arts Proposals, 1972-1973 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 35)
  - Doctorate in Public Affairs (2 Year Colleges Meeting, 1972 October 18-19 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 36)
  - Doctorate in Public Affairs (Statement on Doctorate of Arts in Public Affairs, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 37)
  - Doctor of Arts in Public Affairs, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 38)
  - Master of Arts in Public Affairs (1971-1976) Undergraduate Public Affairs Program (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 39)
  - Master of Arts in Public Affairs (1971-1976) Dr. James Kelly, Public Affairs Program, 1973-1976 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 40)
  - Master of Arts in Public Affairs (1971-1976) Master of Arts Degree in Public Affairs, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 41)
  - Master of Arts in Public Affairs (1971-1976) Letters - MAPA Program (Degree & Non-Degree), ca. 1971 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 42)
  - Public Affairs Advisory Committee (1972-1975) PAF Advisory Committee Meeting, February 21 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 43)
  - Public Affairs Advisory Committee (1972-1975) Public Affairs (Various (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 44)
  - Public Affairs Advisory Committee (1972-1975) Meeting - Public Affairs Advisory Committee Doctorate in Public Affairs, 1973 September 26; 1974 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 45)
  - Public Affairs (1971-1972) Report - Graduate Program in Public Affairs, ca. 1972 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 46)
  - Public Affairs (1971-1972) Ford Foundation Meeting, Public Affairs, 1972 February 14 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 47)
  - Public Affairs (1972-1974) Dean's Day File, Public Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 48)
  - Public Affairs (1972-1974) Distribution of Courses Form, Public Affairs, 1974 Spring (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 49)
  - Public Affairs (1972-1974) Program Descriptions, Public Affairs (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 50)
  - Public Affairs (1973-1977) New Course - Institute in Public Affairs (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 51)
  - Public Affairs (1973-1977) Application & Enrollment Trends, Public Affairs, 1976 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 52)
  - Public Affairs (1973-1977) Proposed Major in Public Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 53)
  - Public Affairs (1973-1977) Proposed Major in Public Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Academic Department and Program Files), Folder 54)
- Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects, 1965-1986; 5; 4.5 cubic ft.
  This subseries consists of material from: Comparative Studies Development Center (CDSC), 1965-1973, 1977-1979; Center for Women in Government (CWIG), 1977-1983, 1986; Institute for Public Policy Alternatives (IPPA), 1973-1975; International Development Program, 1980-1984; Legislative Institute, 1967-1981; Local Government Studies Center, 1957-1972 Public Executive Project (PEP), 1971, 1974, 1975-1980; Public Service Training Program, 1984-ca. 1986; and other centers and institutes, 1973-1981, 1987
  - Comparative Studies Development Center, Dean's Files, 1971-1973 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 1)
  - Comparative Studies Development Center, Dean's Files, 1971-1973 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 2)
  - Comparative Studies Development Center, Dean's Files, 1971-1973 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 3)
  - Comparative Studies Development Center, Dean's Files, 1971-1973 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 4)
  - Comparative Studies Development Center, 1965-1969; 1977-1979 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 5)
  - Center for Women in Government, 1977-1978 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 6)
  - Center for Women in Government, 1979-1980 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 7)
  - Center for Women in Government, 1980-1981 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 8)
  - Center for Women in Government, 1980-1981 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 9)
  - Center for Women in Government, 1980-1981 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 10)
  - Center for Women in Government (CWIG) Publications, 1978-1982; 1986 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 11)
  - Center for Women in Government (CWIG) Board of Director's Reports, 1978-1983 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 12)
  - Center for Women in Government (CWIG) Board of Director's Reports, 1979 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 13)
  - Center for Women in Government (CWIG) Board of Director's Reports, 1980 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 14)
  - Center for Women in Government (CWIG) Board of Director's Reports, 1981 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 15)
  - Institute on Public Policy Alternatives (1973-1975) IPPA Meeting, 1974 March 8 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 16)
  - Institute on Public Policy Alternatives ( 1973-1975) Suggested Areas for Research, March 15, 1974 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 17)
  - Institute on Public Policy Alternatives (1973-1975) IPPA Meeting, August 1, 1974 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 18)
  - Institute for Public Policy Alternatives (IPPA) - Folders Land Use Project, 1974-1975 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 19)
  - Institute for Public Policy Alternatives, Vitae of IPPA Personnel, 1975 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 20)
  - IPPA Internship Program, 1974-1975 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 21)
  - Institute for Public Policy Alternatives, Illicit Enterprise & Public Policy (Research Proposal), 1974 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 22)
  - Institute for Public Policy Alternatives, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 23)
  - International Development Program, 1980-1981 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 24)
  - International Development Program, 1982-1984 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 25)
  - Legislative Institute, 1973; 1975 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 26)
  - Baruch's Proposal - Legislative Administration Program, 1979 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 27)
  - Legislative Institute, 1980 (Box 8 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 28)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, 1957-1958 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, 1959 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, 1960 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, 1961 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, 1962 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, 1963 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, 1964 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 7)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, 1965-1966 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 8)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Digest, 1966 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 9)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Digest, 1967 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 10)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Digest, 1968 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 11)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Digest, 1969 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 12)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Digest, 1970 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Digest & Cumulative Index, 1970 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, Metropolitan Area Digest & Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 9 (5-Centers, Institutes, Programs and Projects), Folder 15)